monsterauto.ca 2013-05-24

# MonsterAuto.ca: Privacy Policy

1\. This Privacy Policy 

  * MonsterAuto.ca is committed to protecting your personal information and other data provided to us via this Web Site. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it contains important information about the use of information that you provide to us. This Privacy Policy explains what information MonsterAuto.ca collects about you, and how we collect and use your information, including setting out the circumstances where we could provide it to third parties. You should also read the separate Terms and Conditions applicable to this Website. 

2\. What information do we collect and what do we do with it? 

  * To take advantage of some of our services (such as setting a Dealer Membership or Posting Online Ads) you will be required to register with the Website. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web Site. 

  * If you choose to advertise on the Website, certain personal information about you will be captured electronically or otherwise. In the event that such personal information or data is part of your online ad, such personal information or data will be posted to the Website, and may by accessed by users of the Website while browsing the Website.

  * We will use the information that we collect to personalize your experience on the Web Site, to help you log on in the future and to continue to use the Web Site. We may need to pass your information to third parties who help us to maintain, administer or develop the Web Site but that information is only given to those third parties for that limited purpose. 

  * We also monitor traffic patterns and usage of our Web Site to help us improve our Web Site design and layout. We may pass this information to our partners or other third parties but it will not contain any personally identifying information. 

  * MonsterAuto.ca may want to contact you to notify you of changes to the Website, special events or new services or products MonsterAuto.ca is offering that we think may interest you. 

  * If you want to update any of your information held by MonsterAuto.ca, you can either make certain changes on-line or you can send an email detailing the required amendments to support@monsterauto.ca

  * MonsterAuto.ca reserves the right to access and disclose personal data or information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly, or to protect itself or its users. 

3\. Sharing of Information with Third Parties 

·        We follow the most stringent security procedures in the storage and disclosure of personal information that you have given us, to prevent unauthorized access to such information. MonsterAuto.ca will not provide your information to third parties for such purposes as unsolicited e-mails for additional products or services.  We only deal with Partners who we are satisfied have appropriate measures to protect data. However, MonsterAuto.ca shall have no liability to you in respect of any breach of security by a third party.

4\. Your Consent 

·        You acknowledge and agree that: 

·        In the course of using this Website or registering with it and any services offered via this Website, certain information about you will be captured electronically or otherwise and transmitted to MonsterAuto.ca or and, potentially, to any third parties as set out above or to third parties who host our web servers or assist us in maintaining this Website; and 

·        MonsterAuto.ca may send your information outside our servers for processing or use in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

·        You consent to the use, storage, or processing of your personal information by MonsterAuto.ca or any third party MonsterAuto.ca uses for carrying out financial transactions with MonsterAuto.ca. 

·        If ordered by a court of competent jurisdiction to provide any of your personal information collected by MonsterAuto.ca as described in this Privacy Policy, you consent to MonsterAuto.ca providing such personal information to that court in accordance with the court's instructions. 

·        By using this Website, you expressly agree to the collection and use of your information as set out above for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. 

5\. Data Protection Indemnity 

  * For the purpose of the Data Protection, you acknowledge that in the course of you advertising goods on our Web Site, certain personal data about your employees, agents or subcontractors or certain personal data of third parties appearing in the advertising you requested to appear on our Web Site may be captured electronically or otherwise by us. If this is the case, you shall ensure that you have obtained the express consent of any employees, agents, subcontractors or any applicable third parties to the transfer of their personal data to us to use, store and process such personal information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, including where such personal data forms part of the advertising and is posted to the Web Site for accessed by users inside and outside of Canada. You shall indemnify MonsterAuto.ca from and against all claims by any employees, agents, subcontractors or any third parties arising out of your failure to obtain the consent described in this paragraph 5. 

6\. Our Responsibilities - How does MonsterAuto.ca protect user information? 

  * When you enter into on-line credit or other payment card transactions (e.g. ordering advertising services on the Website), we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software encrypts the information that you input before it is transmitted to us. To prevent unauthorized access, we follow legally required security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information that you have given to us. This means that sometimes we may ask for proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. 

  * Areas of the Website where transactions are entered into, reviewed or transmitted may be password protected. You can help to preserve your privacy by never sharing your password with anyone else. 

  * We seek to limit our employees' access to your information about you to those employees who need to have such information to service your account. We stress to our employees the confidential nature of user information and the high level of importance that MonsterAuto.ca places on maintaining this confidentiality. 

7\. What are 'Cookies' and how do we use them? 

  * Cookies - What is a Cookie: A cookie is a piece of information that a web site transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard drive On visiting the Website, a cookie will be placed on your computer automatically by MonsterAuto.ca's Website. MonsterAuto.ca may use two types of cookies from time to time: "persistent" cookies and "session" cookies. Session cookies are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the Website and persistent cookies are cookies, which remain in the cookie file of your browser longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie).

  * MonsterAuto.ca's Use of Cookies: MonsterAuto.ca does not use its persistent or session cookies to store personal information about you.  MonsterAuto.ca uses its cookies for monitoring load balancing between its servers while you are linked to the Website, to analyze user traffic, and to perform web log audits. Third party advertisers may serve cookies via this Website but these are only used to serve advertisements from the Website's ad servers and to track whether visitors to the Website click these advertisements.  MonsterAuto.ca may pass the non-personal information collected by its cookies to third parties but only for the purposes of carrying out such monitoring, analysis or web log auditing, or for the purposes of tracking the number or anonymous users of the Web Site.

  * How to reject/deactivate Cookies: Most browsers accept cookies automatically but you have the ability to accept/decline cookies by altering the settings in your browser to prevent automatic acceptance of cookies. If you decline/disable cookies, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of the Website or the Website may not be available to you.

8\. Changes to Privacy Policy 

·        We reserve the right to add to or change the terms of this Privacy Policy, without prior notice to you. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the new Privacy Policy on the Web Site, and it will become effective from the time of posting to the Web Site. Please visit this Privacy Policy on a regular basis to make sure you have read the latest version and you understand what we do with your information. Wherever possible, we will give you notice of any changes prior to their implementation. 

9\. Feedback 

·        If you have any queries or problems with regard to this Privacy Policy or the uses to which we put your information, please e-mail us at support@monsterauto.ca.
